http://www.quadmaniascotland.co.uk/privacy-policy

×Quad Bike TreksClay ShootingArcheryMulti-ActivityFamilyCorporate & GroupsStag & HenGift VouchersAbout UsBooking
Multi Activity Plan your ideal day
FamilyCorporate & GroupsStag & HenGift VouchersAbout UsBooking
Contact
Find Us
Open MenuContact
Privacy PolicyThis website is operated by Quadmania Limited and whose registered address is Stronchullin Farm, Blairmore, Argyll, PA23 8TP. (“We”) are committed to protecting and preserving the privacy of our visitors when visiting our site or communicating electronically with us.This policy sets out how we process any personal data we collect from you or that you provide to us through our website. We confirm that we will keep your information secure and that we will comply fully with all applicable UK Data Protection legislation and regulations. Please read the following carefully to understand what happens to personal data that you choose to provide to us, or that we collect from you when you visit this site. By visiting https://www.quadmaniascotland.co.uk (our website) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.Types of information we may collect from youWe may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information about individuals who visit and use our website:Information you supply to us. You may supply us with information about you by filling in forms on our website. This includes information you provide when you submit a contact form, Booking or Gift Voucher order. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number.Information our website automatically collects about you. With regard to each of your visits to our website we may automatically collect information including the following:technical information, including a truncated and anonymised version of your Internet protocol (IP) address, browser type and version, operating system and platform;information about your visit, including what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got to the site (including date and time); page response times, length of visit, what you click on, documents downloaded and download errors.CookiesOur website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. When someone visits this website we sometimes collect standard internet information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We collect this information in a way which does not personally identify anyone.Almost all web browsers allow control of cookies. This website provides information on how to manage cookies using the settings in your browser:  www.allaboutcookies.orgCookies are widely used to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.The table below explains the cookies we may use, when we use them and why we use them.NamePurposeActivatedExpiresInitiated by this websiteSKRYBWe use it for the search feature which requires the use of cookies to function. The information stored in this cookie is not personally identifiable.On visitWhen you leave the websitecsrfTokenWe use this to ensure the information submitted to our site was entered on our site. The enquiry features require the use of this cookie to function. The information stored in this cookie is not personally identifiable.On visitWhen you leave the websiteInitiated by Google Analytics_gaIf set, this cookie identifies a unique visitor. This allows us to establish if a visitor has been to the website before (returning visitor) or is a new visitor. This is information is not personally identifiable.On visitAfter 2 Years_gidIf set, this cookie establishes a visitor session. This means, for example, our statistics can show us how many pages on average a unique visitor views on our website. This is information is not personally identifiable.On visitAfter 1 Day_gatIf set, this cookie is used to throttle request rate. This is information is not personally identifiable.On visit1 MinuteHow we may use the information we collectWe use the information in the following ways:Information you supply to us. We will use this information:to provide you with information and/or services that you request from us;Information we automatically collect about you. We will use this information:to administer our site including troubleshooting and statistical purposes;to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;security and debugging as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure.This information is collected anonymously and is not linked to information that identifies you as an individual. We use Google Analytics to track this information. Find out how Google uses your data at https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245. [Make this link to the GoogleAnalytics page]Disclosure of your informationAny information you provide to us will either be emailed directly to us or may be stored on a secure server located within the UK. We do not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies.We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal data is not disclosed to regional/national institutions and authorities, unless required by law or other regulations.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.Third party linksOur site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the third party websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.Your rights – access to your personal dataYou have the right to ensure that your personal data is being processed lawfully (“Subject Access Right”). Your subject access right can be exercised in accordance with data protection laws and regulations. Any subject access request must be made in writing to: Quadmania Limited, Stronchullin Farm, Blairmore, Argyll, PA23 8TP. We will provide your personal data to you within the statutory time frames. To enable us to trace any of your personal data that we may be holding, we may need to request further information from you. If you have a complaint about how we have used your information, you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).Changes to our privacy policyAny changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.ContactQuestions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@quadmaniascotland.co.uk.Last updated: 25/06/2019
Stronchullin Farm, Blairmore, By Dunoon, PA23 8TPActivitiesQuad Bike TreksClay ShootingArcheryMulti-ActivityMain PagesFamilyCorporate & GroupsStag & HenGift VouchersAbout UsBookingLegal PrivacyTerms & ConditionsUseful Info Food & DrinkLocal AccomodationCowal PeninsulaSafer StaysLegal PrivacyTerms & ConditionsMenuFind UsCall Us
